

# DANG XUAN QUANG

188/12A Cao Dat, Ward 1, District 5, Ho Chi Minh City · 0908 099 9871

Skype: dangquang0309 · Slack: dangquang3991@gmail.com

Email: dangquang3991@gmail.com · GitHub: jasondang1991

I am Dang Xuan Quang, a Website Developer from Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam. I have experience with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects, I can handle the job of Frontend and Backend position, but most of the time I work with Frontend. Apart from being a website developer, I was also a professional athlete in gymnastics. I have played in many international tournaments, when I retired from being an athlete, I became a true programmer.

#### SKILLS

 Frontend: HTML5/CSS3/SCSS, Javascript, Boostrap, Tailwind (Learning), Angular (Learning), Express.

Backend: PHP, Java, Spring Boot, C#, NodeJS.

• Database: SQL/MYSQL, MongoDB

CMS: WordPress

## **LANGUAGES**

• Languages: Vietnamese, English, German.

# **EXPERIENCE**

**MAR 2015 - JULY 2021** 

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER (REMOTE), PSM MEDIA AGENCY - CHICAGO, ILLINOIS

I have been working full time for the company, I do the frontend work and develop the website and maintain them. As I gained more experience I worked as a backend developer and was allowed to administer the server through wpengine. Most of the websites I work on are in the US market.

MAR 2020 - MAR 2021

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER (REMOTE), PRO REA SOLUTIONS

I develop the website for the company through two platforms Shopify and WordPress, but it is still WordPress, besides, I also provide technical support for my colleagues in the marketing department.

**APRIL 2017 - DEC 2017** 

FRONTEND DEVELOPER (OUTSOURCE), PHOENIX ADVERTISING CO. LTD - HCM,

VIET NAM

Coding and custom of HTML5 newsletter and spam-check support in digital marketing projects of YouTube (newsletter, email campaign).

**DEC 2014 - DEC 2015** 

**WEBSITE DEVELOPER, FREELANCER** 

FEB 2014 - DEC 2014

DIGITAL MARKETING, INSTITUTE OF ADMINISTRATION AND FINANCE (IFA) - HCM, VIET NAM

## **EDUCATION**

AUG 2019 - AUG 2021

# FPT APTECH DIPLOMA – INTERNATIONAL SOFTWARE ENGINEER, FPT ACADEMY INTERNATIONAL (FPT APTECH)

After studying in Germany for a while, but for personal reasons, I stopped everything and returned to my country. After that, I studied and enrolled at FPT Aptech to improve my programming skills & background. then have the opportunity to work on the Backend side.

2011 - 2015

BACHELOR, HO CHI MINH CITY UNIVERSITY OF SPORT

- Focus: gymnastics

- Final grade: good

#### **TEAM & PERSONAL PROJECTS**

- FPT Academy Portal (graduation project): a management system for training, academic, and student
  programs. The system support training room includes modules to create timetables for students, take
  attendance for students, import study program by a year, transfer students, create exam schedules,
  manage exam scores, and module to send feedback for students.
- Marketing Management System: Participating in building frontend marketing management system.
- **E-commerce:** Build some retail websites.
- Portfolio Website: Build some business referral websites.
- **Email Marketing:** Build email marketing template & campaign.